trivia54.com 2011-04-29

# Trivia Today- Trivia

Privacy Policy 

**Policy Last Revised: August 13, 2010.**

The following sets forth the policies for the collection and use of personally identifiable information ("Information") by Trivia Today ("Trivia Today") in connection with its operation of its Web site located at http://www.TriviaToday.com (the "Site"), and supersedes any previous statement of such policies. Trivia Today takes its obligations regarding privacy very seriously, and it wants to ensure users are fully informed about the Information they are providing to it. 

**Collection of Information.**

In connection with the Site, Trivia Today may collect Information in the following ways:

  * Through forms filled out by a user on the Site 
  * Through Information provided by a user in connection with surveys and prize promotion entries 
  * Through the maintenance and analysis of Web server logs 
  * Via e-mail and other communications between a user and Trivia Today 

Trivia Today may also connect non-personally identifiable information from users via "cookies" (small text files placed by Trivia Today on user computers), single-pixel GIF image files (also called "Web beacons"), Web server log analysis and other similar technological means. Such information may be used to track site trends and enhance the user experience, and may be shared with third parties.

To the extent third parties may place advertising on the Site, such third parties may utilize cookies or other technological means within the advertising to collect and utilize non-personally identifiable information. Trivia Today is not responsible for information collected by third parties in this manner, nor for the collection or use of Information by other sites to which the Site is linked.

**Types of Information Collected by Trivia Today.**

The following types of Information about a user are among those that may be collected by Trivia Today in connection with the Site:

  * Name 
  * Postal address 
  * E-mail address 
  * Telephone number 
  * Cell phone number 
  * Age 
  * Date of birth 
  * IP Address 
  * Referring site 
  * Other technical information collected by the Site's servers. 

**No Collection of Information from Children.** The Site is not intended for users under the age of 18, nor does Trivia Today knowingly collect or retain Information in connection with the Site from children under the age of 13. 

**Use of Information.**

Trivia Today may use Information collected in connection with the Site in the following ways:

  * To provide requested information, products and services to users via the Site or through other online or offline channels 
  * To enable users to enter prize promotions and receive prizes from Trivia Today. 
  * To improve the user experience with the Site 
  * In connection with the operation of the Site 
  * For users to obtain information and offers for products and services offered by Trivia Today.

In order to do the foregoing, Trivia Today may provide the Information to trusted third parties, including third party contractors providing services to Trivia Today such as the operation of the Site, communication services and fulfillment of orders, and information verification. Trivia Today will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit use of the Information by such third parties to the specific uses set forth above. Trivia Today also utilizes electronic and physical security to reduce the risk of improper access to or manipulation of Information during transmission and storage, but cannot guarantee the security or integrity of the Information and shall have no liability for breaches of security or integrity or third-party interception in transit. 

Trivia Today may also disclose Information to affiliated entities, when it determines it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or regulations, in connection with a merger, acquisition, asset purchase or sale of or by Trivia Today, or to protect the interests or safety of Trivia Today, its customers, or other visitors to the Site. Opting Out from Offers from Trivia Today. 

At any time, a user may opt out from receiving future offers from Trivia Today through the user's profile on the Site, by following the instructions contained within each marketing communication or by sending an e-mail message to trivia@TriviaToday.com. Such opting out will not apply to any communications from third parties to whom Trivia Today may have provided Information regarding the user. Third parties' use of the Information is subject to such parties' own privacy policies, for which Trivia Today shall not be responsible. 

**Access to Information.**

All users who provide their Information to Trivia Today may modify and correct such Information by e-mailing us at trivia@TriviaToday.com. 

**Your California Privacy Rights.**

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Trivia Today who are California residents to request certain information regarding Trivia Today's disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties' direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to: trivia@TriviaToday.com. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy.**

Trivia Today reserves the right to revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such revisions will be effective on the date of posting to the Site, and will apply to all information collected by Trivia Today both prior to and following the effective date. Your use of the Site following any such revisions will be deemed your acceptance of such revisions. Users should periodically visit this page to review the current policies with regard to Information.
